{
    "subject": "Arthur_Rankin",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "_Jr. The_Hobbit__1977_film_",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Rankin directed _The Hobbit (1977) film_.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9785795211791992,
            "question": "Which film was directed by Arthur Rankin in 1977?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9715737700462341,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Arthur Rankin in 1977?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9489498138427734,
            "question": "Who directed _The Hobbit (1977)_ film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8805885314941406,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Arthur Rankin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8641343116760254,
            "question": "Besides _The Hobbit_, what other films has Arthur Rankin directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.771916925907135,
            "question": "Is Arthur Rankin known for directing animated films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6594429016113281,
            "question": "What year was _The Hobbit_ film released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5973809957504272,
            "question": "Arthur Rankin directed a famous adaptation of what literary work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5776004195213318,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who worked on _The Hobbit_ film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5286391377449036,
            "question": "What kind of media did Arthur Rankin work with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Rankin directed _The Hobbit (1977) film_.",
            "html": "yago_11728_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director who worked on _The Hobbit_ film?",
            "html": "yago_11728_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Rankin directed a famous adaptation of what literary work?",
            "html": "yago_11728_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was _The Hobbit_ film released?",
            "html": "yago_11728_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11728_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"The Hobbit is the name of a 1977 American animated television special from the Rankin/Bass studio, directed by Jules Bass and Arthur Rankin Jr.\" This information supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}